<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[My Octopress Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/"/>
  <updated>2015-08-12T16:18:39-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tech Discoveries]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2015/06/19/tech-discoveries/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-19T10:23:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2015/06/19/tech-discoveries</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
Yesterday I learned some new things that I can add to my tech bag and I was reminded of some old favorites. The academy reminded me of Google Docs. I am still working on learning my way around this feature being that I am old school. Meaning I like carrying flash drives around on my key chain. &nbsp;I learned about Trello and Harvest. I learned about Slacker and played around with my Mac AirBook. I really like that we use Mac in class because it gives me an opportunity to familiarize myself with the system and build a new skill. <br />The opportunity to learn new skills is what attracted me to this program. Yesterday Lupus reared its ugly head and I had to leave class early. &nbsp;I think that I will have to develop a new self-care plan so that I can make it through this class.<br />Before class we discuss what blockers we are facing that could hinder our progress for me that is knowing that my housing is secure. Part of my wanting to be in this class is to get a solid foundation into society. I have lived on the fringes of society my entire life. This class will help me get a career that will allow me to get off of SSI and continue to move towards freedom.<br />Today I returned to class with a box of mint cookies to calm my stomach. I seem to be holding my own now. It is the end of the first week and I can't wait to see what the future holds.</div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fresh Wind, Fresh Fire]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2015/06/17/fresh-wind-fresh-fire/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-17T13:25:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2015/06/17/fresh-wind-fresh-fire</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
Three days into my YWCA YWEB class and I feel like I might get the hang of this after all. Having never seen this before I am proud I have come this far. It is strange looking at code when you've never seen it before. I am trying to figure out if this is something I can grasp enough to carve out a career or maybe use as a spring board to sustain myself while I continue pursuing my passion. I am a writer first and foremost so it will be interesting to see where this thread takes me.<br />Right now I am wondering if I could benefit from Code Academy or Khan Academy so I can immerse myself in this world.</div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Hear the Karma Train Coming..........]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2015/06/12/i-hear-karma-train-coming/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-12T17:30:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2015/06/12/i-hear-karma-train-coming</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
I thought of you as awake; someone I could accept Master Card from until I realized you did not want to be Master nor Commander of your fate.<br /><div>I thought of you as awake; someone I could tear down the walls for until I realized you were a mere mirage; a fake.<br />I thought of you as awake; then I saw you would rather steal from me than build with me.<br />I hear the Karma Train Coming...... moving stealthily unhurried by your arrogance.<br /><br /><br /><br /></div><div><br /></div></div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mourning]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2015/05/31/mourning/"/>
    <updated>2015-05-31T22:49:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2015/05/31/mourning</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
<span style="background-color: white; color: #141823; font-family: helvetica, arial, 'lucida grande', sans-serif; font-size: 14px; line-height: 19.3199996948242px;">Strange; the luxury of silence amid the commotion of grief. That moment you slip among the trees to tell them your troubles; feeling normal is just around the corner yet unable to find its rhythm where you were last. I want to wake up and hear your laugh, see your smile or hear you tell me one more time to be myself. I want your wisdom and love bottled.</span><br /><span style="background-color: white; color: #141823; font-family: helvetica, arial, 'lucida grande', sans-serif; font-size: 14px; line-height: 19.3199996948242px;"><br /></span></div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Came to Love]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2015/05/31/i-came-to-love/"/>
    <updated>2015-05-31T18:43:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2015/05/31/i-came-to-love</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
<span style="background-color: white; color: #141823; font-family: helvetica, arial, 'lucida grande', sans-serif; font-size: 14px; line-height: 19.3199996948242px;">I came to love; came to the acceptance and freedom tucked inside home.</span><br style="background-color: white; color: #141823; font-family: helvetica, arial, 'lucida grande', sans-serif; font-size: 14px; line-height: 19.3199996948242px;" /><span style="background-color: white; color: #141823; font-family: helvetica, arial, 'lucida grande', sans-serif; font-size: 14px; line-height: 19.3199996948242px;">I came to love; came to soak in the warmth of those who don't share my blood yet hear my heart.</span><br style="background-color: white; color: #141823; font-family: helvetica, arial, 'lucida grande', sans-serif; font-size: 14px; line-height: 19.3199996948242px;" /><span style="background-color: white; color: #141823; font-family: helvetica, arial, 'lucida grande', sans-serif; font-size: 14px; line-height: 19.3199996948242px;">I came to love; came to hear her cadence her rhythm granting permission for mine to become softer slowly recalling southern roots.</span><br style="background-color: white; color: #141823; font-family: helvetica, arial, 'lucida grande', sans-serif; font-size: 14px; line-height: 19.3199996948242px;" /><span style="background-color: white; color: #141823; font-family: helvetica, arial, 'lucida grande', sans-serif; font-size: 14px; line-height: 19.3199996948242px;">I came to love; came to watch my nephews curiosity as they explore.</span><br style="background-color: white; color: #141823; font-family: helvetica, arial, 'lucida grande', sans-serif; font-size: 14px; line-height: 19.3199996948242px;" /><span style="background-color: white; color: #141823; font-family: helvetica, arial, 'lucida grande', sans-serif; font-size: 14px; line-height: 19.3199996948242px;">I came to love; came to hear his wisdom for further growing my faith as I continue my journey.</span><span class="text_exposed_show" style="background-color: white; color: #141823; display: inline; font-family: helvetica, arial, 'lucida grande', sans-serif; font-size: 14px; line-height: 19.3199996948242px;"><br />I came to love; came here in a community struggling to stand I came to love.</span><br /><br /><br /><br /><br /></div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Moment the Truth Doesn't Answer the Questions]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2015/01/24/the-moment-truth-doesnt-answer-questions/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-24T19:24:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2015/01/24/the-moment-truth-doesnt-answer-questions</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
Anyone who knows me knows I have struggled to answer one question my entire life; "Who am I?" Growing up in two different foster care systems in two different states has left that question echoing in my brain for many years. Tonight I took a gaint step and did a background check on a former foster parent. However after I saw the information I realized that it was only a small sliver of the puzzle and now I find myself at the moment when the truth doesn't answer the questions. The journey continues...............</div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Cup Runneth Over]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2015/01/19/my-cup-runneth-over/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-19T19:39:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2015/01/19/my-cup-runneth-over</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
Today I did it. I sat face to face with a young lady and explained why she would be wise to take a chance on me. I explained that though my journey has not been a straight one&nbsp;I have made the best of every opportunity. Today I did it. I reached a goal and secured a life while knowing there is more to be done. Today I did it..........then there was the pause.<br />The pause whispered "You are not alone." So I took a deep breath and looked up at the sky murmuring thank you. Thank you for hearing me say that I was willing to put in the hard work. Thank you for guarding the dreams, sheltering the hopes and wiping the tears. Thank you; Universe. Thank you; Karma. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.</div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hennessy Black]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2015/01/19/hennessy-black/"/>
    <updated>2015-01-19T19:23:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2015/01/19/hennessy-black</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
Minds meeting in a tight space pressed between who we are and who we wish to be. A smoother, richer, darker place; can this soft-hearted gangster keep my pace?<br /><div>Beyond being top to my bottom or bottom to my top; can he cause me to enter subspace without removing my clothes? Caress my mind until my soul glows......<br /><br />Minds meeting in a tight space pressed between where we are and where we wish to be.&nbsp;A smoother, richer, darker place; can this soft-hearted gangster see me? <br />Can he honor my requst for time alone; will he allow himself to be my home? Respect these steps taken towards&nbsp;our future; proudly standing at my side?<br /><br />My tongue trips upon itself as I feel these syllables recede to breath. Henessy Black warms my belly and I turn myself towards life's stage seeking to understand my choice.<br /><br /><br />&nbsp;</div></div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saturday September 6th]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/09/06/saturday-september-6th/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-06T23:52:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/09/06/saturday-september-6th</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
A funny thing happened to me as I was working on my memoir. The story I thought &nbsp;I was writing has morphed into something else. &nbsp;Honestly, my first draft was a temper tantrum on paper and my second draft was not much better. I realize now that those first drafts had to be written to reach the vulnerability beneath. I also realize my mental household is shifting. I am shedding the skin of abuse and neglect on a whole different level.<br />I am grateful for the process; I have faith in the process; I will rise through the process. I am thankful.</div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday, September 5th]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/09/05/friday-september-7th/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-05T20:35:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/09/05/friday-september-7th</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
<b><u>Day 12: Labor Intense Gratitude</u></b><br />This morning I had watermelon for breakfast and I was instantly happy. Today I spent time researching general information on ways to move closer to the vegetarian side of things. I am already living in that arena now I want to see if I can become a permanent resident. I only allow myself to have meat once a week because I am afraid that my iron levels will be too low if I remove it completely. Also certain times during the week I will crave seafood; especially fish and shrimp. Honestly, one of the reasons I miss the South so much is the fresh catch of the day. Up here those are just words but at home they are a reality. Sigh. Anyways I am still on the fence food wise so I say I am mostly vegetarian.<br />Food aside; today I sent out recommendation requests for my UW application. Now, all I have to do is send in the requests for transcripts and then it is out of my hands. I am relieved and terrified at the same time. I have reservations about the accessibility of campus but I know it is the only place I can go to receive my majors. Plus I am leaning more and more towards library science for graduate school. Deep breath. I have to become an undergrad first. Smiling at myself because I can already see me working and living in D.C. That is the goal.<br />I am proud that I have taken this step towards shaping my reality. There is a lot of hard work ahead of me but I welcome it. I am thankful today was a good productive day. I look forward to tomorrow.</div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Day 11: Thursday, September 4th, 2014]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/09/04/day-11-thursday-september-4th-2014/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-04T11:26:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/09/04/day-11-thursday-september-4th-2014</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
<b><u>Day 11: It's in the Morning</u></b><br /><b><u><br /></u></b><br /><ol><li>Thankful for music; all kinds, nothing helps lift me more.</li><li>Thankful for the return of my phone.</li><li>Thankful for thunderstorms.</li><li>Thankful for hugs.</li><li>Thankful for laughter.</li><li>Thankful for tenacity.</li><li>Thankful for courage.</li><li>Thankful for financial literacy.</li><li>Thankful for generosity of spirit.</li><li>Thankful for my nieces and nephews.</li><li>Thankful for the fruits of my spirit.</li><li>Thankful for my life.</li><li>Thankful for the lessons learned from Lupus.</li><li>Thankful that the story I thought I was writing has turned into something else.</li><li>Thankful that I make a difference.</li><li>Thankful that a mind is a terrible thing to waste.</li><li>Thankful "It's in the morning."</li><li>Thankful I like myself.</li><li>Thankful I am forever learning myself.</li><li>Thankful I speak my love language.</li><li>Thankful happiness is in the small things.</li><li>Just Thankful to be Thankful.</li></ol>&nbsp;</div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Day & Night 10: September 3rd, 2014]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/09/03/day-10-september-3rd-2014/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-03T20:57:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/09/03/day-10-september-3rd-2014</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
As I prepare to close my eyes tonight I find myself deeply grateful for the passionate curiosity which keeps me searching for my bloodline. I am grateful for following my instinct to write my story down on paper and I am grateful for ignoring the little voice urging me to stop pressing word keys. Today was a hard day because things I thought had been taken rose to the surface; as did the tears.<br />At first I was upset about the tears because I do not cry. Or I did not cry. Now is different. I am finding myself shedding tears more and more as I write. I am grateful because I can cry now and I could not then.<br /><br /></div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Gratitudes September 2, 2014]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/09/02/morning-gratitudes-september-2-2014/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-02T11:04:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/09/02/morning-gratitudes-september-2-2014</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
<b><u>Day 9: September 2, 2014&nbsp;</u></b><br /><br /><ol><li>So thankful for my kind heart.</li><li>So thankful I can control my thoughts and actions.</li><li>So thankful that a fitful night's sleep can transform into a morning of rest.</li><li>So thankful that I am taking steps towards forgiveness through the writing of my memoir.&nbsp;</li><li>So thankful gratitude feeds soul care and soul care feeds gratitude.</li><li>So thankful for the fruits of my spirit.</li><li>So thankful for my eagerness to try new things.</li><li>So thankful for comfort food.</li><li>So thankful for my imagination.</li><li>So thankful for the colors purple and silver.</li><li>So thankful for my library.</li><li>So thankful for my living language Spanish program.</li><li>So thankful I am building a life here in Madison.</li><li>So thankful I am ambitious.</li><li>So thankful I am a child of the sun.</li><li>So thankful for my tenacity.</li><li>So thankful for my curiosity.</li><li>So thankful all things are connected.</li><li>So thankful the Creator is everywhere.</li><li>So thankful I am unafraid of hard work.</li><li>So thankful my name means crown.</li></ol></div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Soul Care #9: Why Gratitude?]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/09/02/soul-care-9-why-gratitude/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-02T11:03:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/09/02/soul-care-9-why-gratitude</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
Anyone who knows me will tell you that I am extremely driven. Being a black woman in America who is differently-abled leaves me no margin of error. I have to be the best because it is the only way I can gain entrance onto a severely slanted playing field. However, the weight of this pressure can cause me to withdraw from people and certain situations. Sometimes when this happens I can be vicious with myself. &nbsp;Telling myself things that if I heard another say to themselves I would admonish them to take it back.<br />I had not really realized that all these months I was required to deal with Lupus and not focus on my passion and purpose I had begun treating myself as the enemy. The fear of another flare had shrunken my world so much that I began thinking I would never....<br />Those three little words are so destructive I hesitate to write them on this page. I am not a woman of fear or doubt. I do not think in that manner. Even as a child when doctors insisted on defining what I could and could not do I was defiant. I have a bucket list that keeps growing as I get older; I speak life to others on a daily basis and yet I could not seem to turn off the negativity inside my head.<br />I knew I was out of control the night I said "Lupus can take me now."<br />I immediately sought the help of a therapist through Catholic Charities. I found that once I was able to articulate my struggles and triumphs to someone aside from my computer my mind started to shift into dreaming again. Dreaming led to planning; planning led to writing down steps which would move me closer to my dream; and this led to me creating daily lists within my phone of tasks to be accomplished.<br />It became easier for me to write about the trauma of my childhood because I had concrete reminders that I was no longer that version of &nbsp;myself. &nbsp;I found that I could write my truth with integrity and not bitterness. Writing was so much a part of me that even when I was not blogging I was writing one word a day. Months went by and slowly three thousand words amassed themselves in ten pages of what is now the fourth draft of my memoir.<br />Recently, I met someone who is constantly providing me with tools to reach my higher self. They challenged me to pay attention to my thoughts and the things I say to myself. It was a difficult realization that I had let the negativity of the past follow me into the present. This realization coupled with a "game" on Facebook sparked the morning and evening gratitudes. As I build myself up again I knew I needed a place I could store them so that if doubt starts to creep in I can shut it down immediately. As I said in one of my earlier posts "having gratitude does not mean life will not hand you lemons; it just means you are better able to make lemonade." Thank you to the person who reminded me of that.<br /><br /></div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evening Gratitudes Monday, September 1, 2014]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/09/01/evening-gratitudes-monday-september-1/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-01T21:34:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/09/01/evening-gratitudes-monday-september-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
<b><u>Evening September 1, 2014</u></b><br /><br /><ol><li>So thankful that I have an abundance of love around me through a select group of people who help guide me to my higher self.</li><li>So thankful that I completed my application to the University of Wisconsin Madison.</li><li>So thankful that I had the strength to clean my kitchen.</li><li>So thankful for a new source of jobs to apply for so that my education can be paid for without loans.</li><li>So thankful for my past volunteer work.</li><li>So thankful for the ability to actualize my dreams.</li><li>So thankful for the ability to ask for what I want.</li><li>So thankful I am here.</li></ol></div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Gratitudes Day 8: Monday, September 1, 2014]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/09/01/morning-gratitudes-day-8-monday/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-01T06:47:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/09/01/morning-gratitudes-day-8-monday</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
<b><u>Day 8: Monday, September 1, 2014</u></b><br /><br /><ol><li>I am thankful for a peaceful nights sleep.</li><li>I am thankful for the ability to help a friend in their time of need.</li><li>I am thankful for the opportunity to apply for admission into the University of Wisconsin Madison.</li><li>I am thankful to have some of what I want and everything I need.</li><li>I am thankful for the opportunity to spend time with my elders.</li><li>I am thankful that my purpose is my passion.&nbsp;</li><li>I am thankful for pen and paper.</li><li>I am thankful for the written word.</li><li>I am thankful for libraries&nbsp;</li><li>I am thankful that hard work always bears fruit.</li></ol><br /><br />Last night I had to help a friend in crisis which prevented me from writing my evening gratitudes. Being grateful does not mean life will not hand me lemons; it means I will be better able to make lemonade. I will continue to post morning and evening gratitudes as well as poetry and Soul Care segments.</div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Organically Grown Love]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/09/01/organically-grown-love/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-01T05:55:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/09/01/organically-grown-love</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
Fertilize tiny seeds of conversation<br />Ferment ideas with hopes and dreams<br />Seek what lies below the A-horizon<br />Plumb the depths of my mind with inquiries<br />Ask what countries I want to see; what languages I speak<br />Challenge me to continue becoming my highest self.<br /><br />When you reach the B-horizon<br />Fertilize me with bone meal<br />Seek to speak my love language<br />Learn why Sundays are my favorite<br />Know that what I ask of you I ask of myself first<br /><br />At the C-horizon<br />Become my partner in peace<br />Let us agree to never take things personally<br />Let us speak with integrity<br />In our ecosystem our word is bond<br /><br />Let us create an environment where kindness and compassion<br />cross-pollinate with strength and ingenuity<br />Where seeds of knowledge become sprouts of wisdom harvested at the appointed time<br />Where the branches of our family tree drop fruits of the spirit in June<br /><br />Imagine answering the ancestors call<br />Let us rebuild<br />My heart swears we can have it all<br /><br /><br /><br /><br /></div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Gratitudes Sunday August 31st]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/08/31/morning-gratitudes-sunday-august-31st/"/>
    <updated>2014-08-31T09:35:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/08/31/morning-gratitudes-sunday-august-31st</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
<b><u>Day 7: Sunday August 31st&nbsp;</u></b><br /><br /><ol><li>Thankful for hip hop because it gave me a home when I lost mine, because it let me know that I was not alone.&nbsp;</li><li>Thankful for warmth and sunshine.</li><li>Thankful for the healing power of a hot shower.</li><li>Thankful for the ability to break bread with a loved one.</li><li>Thankful for Sunday; my favorite day.</li><li>Thankful for calmness.</li><li>Thankful for time to continue my memoir.</li><li>Thankful for the desire to learn.</li><li>Thankful to be able to manifest my desire to learn into things that help my community.</li></ol>The goal today is not to force things. As pressed as I am to make certain changes I know that they will not come through force. I must trust that the doors will open at the appointed time.</div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evening Gratitudes August 30th 2014]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/08/30/evening-gratitudes-august-30th-2014/"/>
    <updated>2014-08-30T22:18:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/08/30/evening-gratitudes-august-30th-2014</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
<b><u>Day 6: August 30th 2014</u></b><br /><b><u><br /></u></b>As this beautiful Saturday draws to a close I find myself happy and smiling. That is all the gratitude right there. So much pain pressed upon my shoulders that I rarely get the chance to remove the labels on me. Today I was just me and happy.</div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Gratitudes August 30th 2014]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/08/30/morning-gratitudes-august-30th-2014/"/>
    <updated>2014-08-30T04:54:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2014/08/30/morning-gratitudes-august-30th-2014</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
<b><u>Day 6: August 30th 2014&nbsp;</u></b><br /><br /><ol><li>I am thankful for access for Lupus medication while I study and learn a more holistic approach to healing my immune system.</li><li>I am thankful for the soothing sounds of jazz floating through my apartment as I prepare to begin my day.</li><li>I am thankful for the kettle filled with water whistling for me to turn it into my morning dose of caffeine.</li><li>I am thankful for a new piece of poetry restlessly urging that it be placed on paper.</li><li>I am thankful for the time to continue writing my memoir today.</li><li>I am thankful for my sense of humor.&nbsp;</li><li>I am thankful the strength to do my household chores.</li><li>I am thankful for the wonderful aromas of breakfast I will soon be preparing.</li></ol>Every day has a new flavor as I strive to increase the tools in my soul care arsenal I plan to savor each one.<ol></ol></div>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
