<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Current Events | My Octopress Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/categories/current-events/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/"/>
  <updated>2015-08-12T15:55:07-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Santa Claus]]></title>
    <link href="http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2013/12/17/santa-claus/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-17T12:27:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://stephanniepb.github.io/honeyblog/blog/2013/12/17/santa-claus</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class='post'>
I do not have television which means that I am rarely accosted by the media and what they call news. However I do have a computer with internet access and I also have a Facebook page which is filled with other pages that I really like, for example The Daily Show. Recently they have been discussing the war on Christmas and the remarks of some of the big network anchormen and women.<br />Now, just for the record, for me the mythical Santa Claus has always been a black man. When I was a little girl I slipped downstairs and watched "Santa" pull toys and other treats from his big red sack. This memory and many more are gold threads in my life's tapestry and even when I lost my community at age nine I never lost the truth about myself or my people.<br />Let's be honest, the fact that major network anchors are concerned about the ethnicity of "Santa" is as laughable as it is disturbing. More disturbing however is the fact that an anchor person is allowed to say the following words "Just because it makes you feel uncomfortable, doesn't mean it has to change." without anyone except Comedy Central's Jon Stewart holding the person accountable for their words. Americans need to do better.</div>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
